Ismay, Lou; Papers ua902.064
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
Louis Ismay Papers
1959-1977
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
Ismay, Louis F.
ua902.064
29.14 cubic ft. 11 Cassettes, 1 reel-to-reel tape
The papers of Lou Ismay document the history of the Environmental Forum at the University at Albany, SUNY, (State University of New York at Albany as it was then known) from 1969-1977, as well as the Environmental Studies Program. The collection contains information on the Environmental Forum, the Protect Your Environment Club, administrative files, student writings, subject files, correspondence, and publications. The student writings are from Ismay’s Environmental Forum classes from 1969-1977. This series is restricted from use, along with parts of the Environmental Forum and correspondence series. This course was held under different numbers during its existence, including A&S 201 and Env.250a and b. The strength of the collection lies not in the educational departments that are represented by the collection, but by the overall impression one can gather about the rise of environmental awareness among students at the university. Access to certain student material is restricted. Consult a staff member for details.
Biographical Sketch
Louis Fletcher Ismay (commonly known as Lou Ismay) was born in Bronxville, New York on February 25, 1925. Ismay received a Bachelor of Education from the University of the State of New York at New Paltz in 1949, and a Master of Arts in education administration from Columbia University in 1958. Prior to finishing his education Ismay served in the military from September 1943 through June 1946. Ismay was selected to be the coordinator of the Environmental Forum course at the State University of New York at Albany (as the University at Albany, SUNY was then known) in 1970 because of his extensive history and experience in administrative, educational, as well as executive positions that required creative and visionary approaches to maximize resources. [Resume of Louis Ismay, undated. Series 1: Environmental Forum, Box 2, Folder 40].
The Environmental Forum course taught by Ismay was a part of the Environmental Studies Program at the University. Additional information about the Environmental Studies Program is available in the finding aid for the collection. Ismay taught the course from its inception in the spring of 1970, when the environmental ideals that this course was based on were spreading to campuses nationwide, until its demise in 1977 because of budget cuts. The themes of the course included new measures for waste management through recycling, strengthening pollution regulations, and reducing unnecessary consumption by individuals. Ismay taught students to take a proactive stance to their surroundings, both environmental and societal, which is reflected in the student projects in this collection. Ismay's students did not passively observe their surroundings, but went out armed with ideas and came back with environmental awareness that they then tried to share with others. Ismay currently lives in Altamont, New York.
Scope and Contents
The Louis Ismay Papers document the history of the Environmental Forum at the State University of New York at Albany (as the University at Albany, SUNY was then known) from 1970-1977, as well as the Environmental Studies Program. The collection contains information on the Environmental Forum, the Protect Your Environment Club (PYE), administrative files, student writings, subject files, correspondence, and publications. The student writings are from Ismay's Environmental Forum classes from 1970-1977. This series, along with parts of the Environmental Forum and correspondence series, is restricted from use. This course was held under different numbers during its existence, including A&S 201 and Env.250a and b.
Many environmental issues facing the Capital Region, as well as the nation between 1968 and 1977, are documented in the Ismay Papers. Recycling, pollution control, consumption reduction, and environmental awareness are all topics that can be found not only in the subject files of the papers, but also in each series. The Environmental Forum was created as a result of the environmental concern that swept through universities on a national level during this time. The purpose of the Forum was active involvement of environmentally concerned individuals with their community in an attempt to better the environment that they lived in. Some papers appear to be from environmental law classes and other related classes. This makes it seem that this collection includes papers from other professors in the Environmental Studies Program, including Rosemary Nichols, an instructor of the law classes.
The collection lacks biographical information of significance about Lou Ismay. Other than learning about a few of his interests, little personal information can be found in his papers. Many of the documents in the collection are damaged as a result of poor storage prior to arriving at the University at Albany. The strength of the collection lies not in the educational departments that are represented in the collection, but in the overall impression of the rise of environmental awareness among students at the University at Albany, which is one small link to understanding the rise in environmental concern on campuses throughout the United States during this period. This can be seen through national events such as Earth Day and Earth Week that were begun in this era (see Governor Malcolm Wilson executive order creating Earth Week in 1974 in series 2).
Arrangement of the Collection
The collection is organized as follows:
Acquisition Information
All items in this manuscript group were donated to the University Libraries, M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives, by Louis Ismay in April 2005.
Related Materials
Related collections in the M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives can be found in the subject guides for Conservation and the Environment, University Archives Administrative Records and Faculty, Students, and Alumni/ae. Of particular interest are the collections of Jackson Davis (APAP-141), Robert Rienow (UA-902.009), Vincent Schaefer (UA-902.010), and the Environmental Studies Program (UA-XXX.001).
Access
Access unrestricted with exceptions to 10 folders labeled "personal student information" in Series 1, all of the student writings in Series 4, and 1 folder labeled "Student Mail, Personal" in Series 6. Consult a staff member for details.
Conservation and the Environment; Albany, New York; Environmental policy--New York (State); Environmental education--New York (State); Conservation of natural resources--New York (State)--Citizen participation; Correspondence; Clippings; Photographs; Slides; Manuscripts; Memoranda; UAlbany Faculty & Alumni Papers; State University of New York at Albany--Environmental Studies Program
- Environmental Forum, 1969-1977; Undated; 1; 3 cubic ft.
  Scope and Contents
  This series documents the entire history of the Environmental Forum at the University at Albany, SUNY from 1969-1977. The Environmental Forum was a course in the Environmental Studies Program at the University at Albany. The purpose of the course was for students to examine the problems created by an overcrowded society in relation to the environment and man. The inter-disciplinary approach the Forum took allowed anyone to take the class, no matter their academic background. The design of the course sent students out into the community to do hands-on projects. Course handouts, in-class assignments, evaluations, and other material comprise the bulk of this series.
  Some of the information in this series is restricted. The restricted folders are labeled "personal student information" and contain confidential information, such as social security numbers.
  Arrangement
  Arranged alphabetically.
  - The 1996 Priority Waterbodies List (Box 1 (1-Environmental Forum), Folder 1)
  - Additional Expenses, 1969 (Box 1 (1-Environmental Forum), Folder 1)
  - Applications, 1975 (Box 1 (1-Environmental Forum), Folder 2)
  - Applications, 1976 (Box 1 (1-Environmental Forum), Folder 3)
  - Attendance, 1974 (Box 1 (1-Environmental Forum), Folder 4)
  - Biographical Sketches, 1969 Fall; 1970 Spring; 1970 Fall (Box 1 (1-Environmental Forum), Folder 5)
  - Biographical Sketches, 1970 Fall; 1971 Spring (Box 1 (1-Environmental Forum), Folder 6)
  - Biographical Sketches, 1971 Fall; 1972 Spring (Box 1 (1-Environmental Forum), Folder 7)
  - Biographical Sketches, 1972 Fall; 1973 Spring (Box 1 (1-Environmental Forum), Folder 8)
  - Biographical Sketches, 1973 Fall; 1974 Spring (Box 1 (1-Environmental Forum), Folder 9)
  - Biographical Sketches, 1974 Summer (Box 1 (1-Environmental Forum), Folder 10)
  - Biographical Sketches, 1974 Fall (Box 1 (1-Environmental Forum), Folder 11)
  - Biographical Sketches, 1976 Summer (Box 1 (1-Environmental Forum), Folder 12)
  - Biographical Sketches, 1976 Fall (Box 1 (1-Environmental Forum), Folder 13)
  - Biographical Sketches, 1977 Spring (Box 1 (1-Environmental Forum), Folder 14)
  - City Of Cohoes Field Trip, Undated (Box 1 (1-Environmental Forum), Folder 15)
  - Class Facts, 1969 (Box 1 (1-Environmental Forum), Folder 16)
  - Conservation, 1972 (Box 1 (1-Environmental Forum), Folder 17)
  - Contacts, 1970 (Box 1 (1-Environmental Forum), Folder 18)
  - Course Attendance, 1970 (Box 1 (1-Environmental Forum), Folder 19-20)
  - Course Evaluations, 1973 (Box 1 (1-Environmental Forum), Folder 21)
  - Course Evaluations, 1974 (Box 1 (1-Environmental Forum), Folder 22)
  - Course Evaluations, 1975 (Box 1 (1-Environmental Forum), Folder 23-25)
  - Course Evaluations, 1976 (Box 1 (1-Environmental Forum), Folder 26-28)
  - Course Evaluations, 1977 (Box 1 (1-Environmental Forum), Folder 29)
  - Course Handouts, 1969-1970 (Box 1 (1-Environmental Forum), Folder 30)
  - Course Handouts, 1974 (Box 1 (1-Environmental Forum), Folder 31)
  - Course Handouts and Environmental Issues, 1970; 1973; 1976 (Box 1 (1-Environmental Forum), Folder 32)
  - Course Statistics, 1970 (Box 1 (1-Environmental Forum), Folder 33)
  - Course Statistics, 1977 (Box 1 (1-Environmental Forum), Folder 34)
  - Environmental Education Our Hope For Survival, 1970 (Box 1 (1-Environmental Forum), Folder 35)
  - Environmental Impact, 1971 (Box 1 (1-Environmental Forum), Folder 36)
  - Exam, 1970 (Box 1 (1-Environmental Forum), Folder 37)
  - Fall, 1974 (Box 1 (1-Environmental Forum), Folder 38)
  - Forum Problems, Undated (Box 1 (1-Environmental Forum), Folder 39)
  - Grant Proposal, 1975 (Box 1 (1-Environmental Forum), Folder 40)
  - Guidelines, 1969 (Box 1 (1-Environmental Forum), Folder 41)
  - Instructor Evaluations, 1974 (Box 2 (1-Environmental Forum), Folder 1)
  - Instructor Evaluations, Undated (Box 2 (1-Environmental Forum), Folder 2-4)
  - Library of Congress Headings for Environment Readings, Undated (Box 2 (1-Environmental Forum), Folder 5)
  - Meal Charges, Undated (Box 2 (1-Environmental Forum), Folder 6)
  - Memos, Proposals, and Lecturer Handouts, 1969-1977 (Box 2 (1-Environmental Forum), Folder 7)
  - Midterm Review Questions, Undated (Box 2 (1-Environmental Forum), Folder 8)
  - Modifications to Forums, 1973 (Box 2 (1-Environmental Forum), Folder 9)
  - Mt. Marcey Field Trip, 1971 (Box 2 (1-Environmental Forum), Folder 10)
  - National Science Foundation Grant, Undated (Box 2 (1-Environmental Forum), Folder 11)
  - Nichols, Rosemary, The Conservation Commission and Open Space Plans, 1976 (Box 2 (1-Environmental Forum), Folder 12)
  - Nichols, Rosemary, (Professor) Environmental Law Cases and Commentary, 1975 (Box 2 (1-Environmental Forum), Folder 13)
  - Notes, Undated (Box 2 (1-Environmental Forum), Folder 14-15)
  - Outline of Forum, 1969-1970 (Box 2 (1-Environmental Forum), Folder 16)
  - Outline and Related Material, 1969 (Box 2 (1-Environmental Forum), Folder 17)
  - Personal Student Information, 1970 (Box 2 (1-Environmental Forum), Folder 18)
  - Personal Student Information, 1971 (Box 2 (1-Environmental Forum), Folder 19-20)
  - Personal Student Information, 1972 (Box 2 (1-Environmental Forum), Folder 21)
  - Personal Student Information, 1973 (Box 2 (1-Environmental Forum), Folder 22)
  - Personal Student Information, 1974 (Box 2 (1-Environmental Forum), Folder 23)
  - Personal Student Information, 1975 (Box 2 (1-Environmental Forum), Folder 24)
  - Personal Student Information, 1976 (Box 2 (1-Environmental Forum), Folder 25)
  - Personal Student Information, Undated (Box 2 (1-Environmental Forum), Folder 26)
  - Personal Student Information, Student Applications, 1972; 1974; 1975; 1977 (Box 2 (1-Environmental Forum), Folder 27)
  - Petitions to Continue Forum, Undated (Box 2 (1-Environmental Forum), Folder 28)
  - Photographs, Undated (Box 2 (1-Environmental Forum), Folder 29-30)
  - Pine Bush Conservancy Movement, 1971 (Box 2 (1-Environmental Forum), Folder 31)
  - Planning for Forum, 1970 (Box 2 (1-Environmental Forum), Folder 32)
  - Program Approval, 1969 August 1 (Box 2 (1-Environmental Forum), Folder 33)
  - A Proposal to Initiate The Environmental Forum, 1969 (Box 2 (1-Environmental Forum), Folder 34)
  - Receipts, 1974 (Box 2 (1-Environmental Forum), Folder 35)
  - Renshaw, Edward, The Energy Crisis on Balance was a Good Thing, Undated (Box 2 (1-Environmental Forum), Folder 36)
  - A Report on Air and Water Pollution by Brian Dickey, 1970 (Box 2 (1-Environmental Forum), Folder 37)
  - Report from Robert LaFleur, 1971 (Box 2 (1-Environmental Forum), Folder 38)
  - Results of Forum Survey Topics, 1974 (Box 2 (1-Environmental Forum), Folder 39)
  - Resume of Louis Ismay, Undated (Box 2 (1-Environmental Forum), Folder 40)
  - Review of Forum, 1969-1970 (Box 2 (1-Environmental Forum), Folder 41)
  - Rittner, Don, Research Report, 1970 (Box 2 (1-Environmental Forum), Folder 42)
  - The Sayings of Chairman Lou, 1970 (Box 3 (1-Environmental Forum), Folder 1)
  - Speaker: Dr. Jack J. Bulloff, 1971 (Box 3 (1-Environmental Forum), Folder 2)
  - Speaker Evaluations, 1970 (Box 3 (1-Environmental Forum), Folder 3)
  - Speaker Evaluations, 1971 (Box 3 (1-Environmental Forum), Folder 4)
  - Speaker Evaluations, 1972 (Box 3 (1-Environmental Forum), Folder 5)
  - Speaker Evaluations, 1973 (Box 3 (1-Environmental Forum), Folder 6)
  - Speaker Evaluations, 1974 (Box 3 (1-Environmental Forum), Folder 7)
  - Speaker Evaluations, 1975 (Box 3 (1-Environmental Forum), Folder 8)
  - Speaker Evaluations, 1976 Fall (Box 3 (1-Environmental Forum), Folder 9)
  - Speaker Evaluations, 1976 (Box 3 (1-Environmental Forum), Folder 10)
  - Speaker Evaluations, 1977 (Box 3 (1-Environmental Forum), Folder 11)
  - Speakers, Undated (Box 3 (1-Environmental Forum), Folder 12)
  - Specimen Examination, 1970 (Box 3 (1-Environmental Forum), Folder 13)
  - Speech by Ismay, Undated (Box 3 (1-Environmental Forum), Folder 14)
  - Student Events, 1975 (Box 3 (1-Environmental Forum), Folder 15)
  - Student Schedules, 1975 (Box 3 (1-Environmental Forum), Folder 16)
  - Student Schedules, Undated (Box 3 (1-Environmental Forum), Folder 17)
  - Student Topics, 1974 (Box 3 (1-Environmental Forum), Folder 18)
  - Student Topics, 1974-1975 (Box 3 (1-Environmental Forum), Folder 19)
  - Student Topics, 1976 (Box 3 (1-Environmental Forum), Folder 20)
  - Student Topics, Undated (Box 3 (1-Environmental Forum), Folder 21)
  - Summary Statements 1, 1969 Fall (Box 3 (1-Environmental Forum), Folder 22)
  - Summary Statements 2, 1969 Fall (Box 3 (1-Environmental Forum), Folder 23)
  - Summary Statements, 1969 (Box 3 (1-Environmental Forum), Folder 24)
  - Summary Statements, 1970 Fall (Box 3 (1-Environmental Forum), Folder 25)
  - Summary Statements, 1970 Spring (Box 3 (1-Environmental Forum), Folder 26)
  - Summary Statements, Undated (Box 3 (1-Environmental Forum), Folder 27)
  - Summer, 1971 (Box 3 (1-Environmental Forum), Folder 28)
  - Summer, 1975 (Box 3 (1-Environmental Forum), Folder 29)
- Protect Your Environment Club (PYE), 1969-1977; Undated; 2; 1.35 cubic ft.
  Protect Your Environment (PYE) was a club at the University at Albany, SUNY, that was an off-shoot of the Environmental Forum. The club was formed in 1969 based on an example from the Thomas School in Connecticut. The club promoted environmental awareness through activities such as teach-ins and Earth Day. In 1974, the club helped to convince Governor Malcolm Wilson to declare a week in April as Earth Week. A framed certificate of the declaration is in the series. This declaration, along with other material too large for standard archival boxes are in a separate flat box. A glass, pink pig head mounted to a wooden board is also part of the series, along with PYE handouts and flyers, the club's constitution, receipts, bills, and other material.
  - Advertisement Flyers, Undated (Box 1 (2-Protect Your Environment Club (PYE)), Folder 1)
  - Bank Statements, 1970-1971 (Box 1 (2-Protect Your Environment Club (PYE)), Folder 2)
  - Boise Cascade, 1970 (Box 1 (2-Protect Your Environment Club (PYE)), Folder 3)
  - Committee on Environmental Studies, 1971 (Box 1 (2-Protect Your Environment Club (PYE)), Folder 4)
  - Community Relations, 1970-1971 (Box 1 (2-Protect Your Environment Club (PYE)), Folder 5)
  - Constitution, 1972 (Box 1 (2-Protect Your Environment Club (PYE)), Folder 6)
  - Contacts, 1973 (Box 1 (2-Protect Your Environment Club (PYE)), Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1971-1972 (Box 1 (2-Protect Your Environment Club (PYE)), Folder 8)
  - Environmental Student Lobby, 1971 (Box 1 (2-Protect Your Environment Club (PYE)), Folder 9)
  - Flyers, Undated (Box 1 (2-Protect Your Environment Club (PYE)), Folder 10)
  - Handbook, Undated (Box 1 (2-Protect Your Environment Club (PYE)), Folder 11)
  - Lab Supply List, Undated (Box 1 (2-Protect Your Environment Club (PYE)), Folder 12)
  - Newsletters of PYE, 1971-1974 (Box 1 (2-Protect Your Environment Club (PYE)), Folder 13)
  - Organization Contacts, 1972 (Box 1 (2-Protect Your Environment Club (PYE)), Folder 14)
  - Organization Membership, 1975 (Box 1 (2-Protect Your Environment Club (PYE)), Folder 15)
  - Photographs PYE Club, Undated (Box 1 (2-Protect Your Environment Club (PYE)), Folder 16)
  - Posters, Undated (Box 1 (2-Protect Your Environment Club (PYE)), Folder 17)
  - Preparing Reports, 1970 (Box 1 (2-Protect Your Environment Club (PYE)), Folder 18)
  - Projects, 1975 (Box 1 (2-Protect Your Environment Club (PYE)), Folder 19)
  - Protect Your Environment Mail, 1977 (Box 1 (2-Protect Your Environment Club (PYE)), Folder 20)
  - Protect Your Environment Policies, 1971-1972 (Box 1 (2-Protect Your Environment Club (PYE)), Folder 21)
  - Public Education, 1971 (Box 1 (2-Protect Your Environment Club (PYE)), Folder 22)
  - PYE Flyers and Organizational Material, 1970 (Box 1 (2-Protect Your Environment Club (PYE)), Folder 23)
  - PYE History, 1970-1971; 1973 (Box 1 (2-Protect Your Environment Club (PYE)), Folder 24)
  - PYE Literature, 1969; 1970; 1975 (Box 1 (2-Protect Your Environment Club (PYE)), Folder 25)
  - PYE and Teach-In, 1970 (Box 1 (2-Protect Your Environment Club (PYE)), Folder 26)
  - Receipts and Bills, 1970-1971 (Box 1 (2-Protect Your Environment Club (PYE)), Folder 27)
  - Receipts and Bills, 1970-1974 (Box 1 (2-Protect Your Environment Club (PYE)), Folder 28)
  - Receipts and Bills, 1971-1972; 1976-1977 (Box 1 (2-Protect Your Environment Club (PYE)), Folder 29)
  - Receipts and Bills, 1973-1974 (Box 1 (2-Protect Your Environment Club (PYE)), Folder 30)
  - Receipts and Bills, 1973-1975 (Box 1 (2-Protect Your Environment Club (PYE)), Folder 31)
  - Receipts and Bills, 1973-1976 (Box 1 (2-Protect Your Environment Club (PYE)), Folder 32)
  - Receipts and Bills, 1975-1976 (Box 1 (2-Protect Your Environment Club (PYE)), Folder 33)
  - Solar Energy Legislation, 1977 (Box 1 (2-Protect Your Environment Club (PYE)), Folder 34)
  - Steering Committee Meetings and Agendas, 1971 (Box 1 (2-Protect Your Environment Club (PYE)), Folder 35)
  - Task Force, 1970 (Box 1 (2-Protect Your Environment Club (PYE)), Folder 36)
  - Thomas School PYE Club, 1969 (Box 1 (2-Protect Your Environment Club (PYE)), Folder 37)
  - PYE Symbol Yellow Cardboard Signs, Undated (Oversized 1, Folder 1)
    8 total signs with 7 containing additional writing.
  - The Kidney Foundation's 1st Annual Hike-A-Thon, 4 copies with writing on back of 3, Undated (Oversized 1, Folder 2)
  - Proclamation, State of New York Executive Chamber, framed declaration of Earth Week by Governor Malcolm Wilson, 1974 (Oversized 1, Folder 3)
  - Protect Your Environment Club Poster, Undated (Oversized 1, Folder 4)
  - Ephemera, 2.42
    - Pigs head sculpture mounted on wooden board, Undated
- Administrative Files, 1969-1977; Undated; 3; 1.33 cubic ft.
  A large portion of this series is about the Environmental Studies Program at the University at Albany, SUNY. Faculty information, course and program proposals, changes in student registration procedures, and changes in class information can all be found in this series.
  - Amendments to the Faculty By Laws, 1974 (Box 1 (3-Administrative Files), Folder 1)
  - Budget Statistics, 1975 (Box 1 (3-Administrative Files), Folder 2)
  - Committee of Concerned Faculty, 1976 (Box 1 (3-Administrative Files), Folder 3)
  - Course Proposal For Arts and Sciences, Undated (Box 1 (3-Administrative Files), Folder 4)
  - Curriculum Material for Environmental Studies, 1970 (Box 1 (3-Administrative Files), Folder 5)
  - Environmental Program Steering Committee, 1971 (Box 1 (3-Administrative Files), Folder 6)
  - Environmental Studies Program, 1971-1972 (Box 1 (3-Administrative Files), Folder 7)
  - Environmental Studies Program, 1973 (Box 1 (3-Administrative Files), Folder 8)
  - Environmental Studies Program, 1974 (Box 1 (3-Administrative Files), Folder 9)
  - Environmental Studies Program, Advisement, 1976 (Box 1 (3-Administrative Files), Folder 10)
  - Environmental Studies Program, Advisory Committee, 1970-1971 (Box 1 (3-Administrative Files), Folder 11)
  - Environmental Studies Program, Committees Budgets Proposals, 1970-1971 (Box 1 (3-Administrative Files), Folder 12)
  - Environmental Studies Program, Courses, 1972 (Box 1 (3-Administrative Files), Folder 13)
  - Environmental Studies Program, Description, Requirements, Courses, Undated (Box 1 (3-Administrative Files), Folder 14)
  - Environmental Studies Program, Draft of Proposal, Undated (Box 1 (3-Administrative Files), Folder 15)
  - Environmental Studies Program, Interdisciplinary Major, 1971-1973 (Box 1 (3-Administrative Files), Folder 16)
  - Environmental Studies Program, Interdisciplinary Majors, Undated (Box 1 (3-Administrative Files), Folder 17)
  - Environmental Studies Program, List of Courses, Undated (Box 1 (3-Administrative Files), Folder 18)
  - Environmental Studies Program, Original Course Outline, 1975 (Box 1 (3-Administrative Files), Folder 19)
  - Environmental Studies Program, Outline, 1972 (Box 1 (3-Administrative Files), Folder 20)
  - Environmental Studies Program, Proposals, 1971 (Box 1 (3-Administrative Files), Folder 21)
  - Environmental Studies Program, Recommendations for, Undated (Box 1 (3-Administrative Files), Folder 22)
  - Environmental Studies Program, Student Guide and Proposal, 1971-1972 (Box 1 (3-Administrative Files), Folder 23)
  - Environmental Studies Response to Recommendations of Presidential Task Force, 1976 (Box 1 (3-Administrative Files), Folder 24)
  - ESEA Proposal Sheets, 1972 (Box 1 (3-Administrative Files), Folder 25)
  - Evaluation of Courses and Instructors, 1973 (Box 1 (3-Administrative Files), Folder 26)
  - Exit Interview Project, 1977 (Box 1 (3-Administrative Files), Folder 27)
  - Faculty, 1973 (Box 1 (3-Administrative Files), Folder 28)
  - Faculty Meetings of the Art Department, 1969-1974 (Box 1 (3-Administrative Files), Folder 29)